[whooshing sound effects]
[music plays]
[Isabel:] My name is Isabeland I live in Caulfield.
Comparing Steamy's to others, I've had a wonderful experience.
They left the carpet virtually walkable on it straightaway.
It wasn't, it didn't feel wet.There was no smell afterwards.
They used these little utensils to putunderneath my furniture to help the carpet dry.
So, once it's dry, it doesn't leave stainswhen the furniture goes back on.
So, now my carpets look fantastic.
All the stains are gone, the shine of theoriginal carpet has actually come through.
I will definitely call them again.
In fact, I've already given their number out to several of my friends.
[Gidon:] At Steamy's, we take pride in our work.
This is why we make sure we have the bestequipment, products and training available.
We don't rush from job to job.
We take our time to give you the best service you deserve.
Backed with a 100% satisfaction guarantee.
[music plays]
[Captioning services provided by amara.org]